Contact

7728825075 (Mobile) senseipeto@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/michael-petomha-msn-rn-cen-cmsrn-17a2342b (LinkedIn) ufhealth.org (Company)

Top Skills

Nursing Education

BLS

ACLS

Michael Peto MHA, MSN, RN, CEN, CMSRN

Nurse Manager of Nursing Resource Office at UF Health Jacksonville

Jacksonville, Florida

Summary

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Management, Emergency Nursing, Nursing Education, Medication Administration. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's in Health Administration focused in Health/Health Care Administration/Management from University of Phoenix.

Experience

UF Health Jacksonville 1 year 9 months

Nurse Manager of Nursing Resource Office March 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months) Jacksonville, Florida

Nursing Supervisor October 2018 - March 2019 (6 months) Jacksonville, Florida

Orange Park Medical Center 5 years 9 months

Nurse Manager of Inpatient Rehabilitation April 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 6 months) Orange Park, Florida

RN Administrative Supervisor January 2013 - April 2017 (4 years 4 months) Orange Park Medical Center

Coordinated Power and Fitness Master Instructor/Owner March 2011 - February 2013 (2 years)

Page 1 of 2

Port Saint Lucie, Florida

4th Degree Black Belt in Hapkido

HCA East Florida Division Workforce and Organizational Development
Adjunct Instructor
August 2010 - January 2013 (2 years 6 months)
West Palm Beach Area, Florida

HCA

ER Trauma Nurse July 2008 - January 2013 (4 years 7 months) Lawn wood Regional & Orange Park Medical Center

Hapkido School of Indomitable Spirit
Master Instructor/Owner
February 2004 - September 2007 (3 years 8 months)
Westlake, Ohio

Education

University of Phoenix MHA/MSN, Health/Health Care Administration/Management · (2015 - 2017)

University of Phoenix
Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Nursing · (2013 - 2015)

Cuyahoga Community College
Associate of Arts and Sciences (A.A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2001 - 2003)